Guide to the New York Community Trust Records 1919-2024 MS 3246
New-York Historical Society
- Series 5: Media and marketing, 1923-2024
  - Sub-series 4: Press clippings, 1934-2024
    - Press clippings, 1934-1967, 1998-1999 (Offsite-box 5.4.1, Folder 1-5)
      Folder 1: Articles on community trusts, 1934-1999
      Folder 2: Articles on community trusts, 1934-1966
      Folder 3: Press clippings -- NYCT/CFI; The James Foundation, 1946-1967
      Folder 4: Press clippings -- NYCT/CFI, 1998
      Folder 5: Press clippings -- NYCT/CFI, 1999
    - Press clippings -- NYCT/CFI, 2000-2004 (Offsite-box 5.4.2)
    - Press clippings -- NYCT/CFI, 2005-2008 (Offsite-box 5.4.3)
    - Press clippings -- NYCT/CFI, 2009-2010 (Offsite-box 5.4.4)
    - Press clippings -- NYCT/CFI, 2011-2012 (Offsite-box 5.4.5)
    - Press clippings -- NYCT/CFI, 2013-2017 (Offsite-box 5.4.6)
    - Press clippings -- NYCT/CFI, 2018-August 2022 (Offsite-box 5.4.7)
    - Press clippings -- NYCT/CFI, September 2022-November 2024 (Offsite-box 5.4.8)
  - Sub-series 5: Advertisements and marketing, 1988-2024
    - Advertisements and marketing, 1988-2016 (Offsite-box 5.5.1, Folder 1-28)
      Folder 1: Marketing analysis, The New York Community Trust: Analysis of New Business Efforts, Final Report, submitted by Peat Marwick Main & Co., May 1988
      Folder 2: 1990 Business Development Program, 1990
      Folder 3: NYCT advertisements, 1990
      Folder 4: NYCT advertisements; NYCT marketing case study, 1992
      Folder 5: NYCT advertisements; NYCT marketing case study, 1993
      Folder 6: NYCT advertisements, 1994
      Folder 7: NYCT advertisements, 1996
      Folder 8: NYCT advertisements, 1997
      Folder 9: NYCT publications reports, December 1998-August 2001
      Folder 10: NYCT advertisements, ca. 1999
      Folder 11: NYCT marketing and new business development, 2000-2021
      Folder 12: NYCT advertisements, 2000
      Folder 13: Transforming the Chicago Community Trust: Learning from the Field, prepared for participants in the CCT Best Practice's Study, December 18, 2000
      Folder 14: NYCT advertisements, 2001
      Folder 15: NYCT advertisements, 2002
      Folder 16: NYCT advertisements; NYCT Strategic Communications Plan, 2003
      Folder 17: NYCT Donor Cultivation Plan, May 17, 2006
      Folder 18: NYCT advertisements, ca. 2007
      Folder 19: NYCT advertisements, 2008
      Folder 20: NYCT advertisements, 2009
      Folder 21: NYCT advertisements, 2010
      Folder 22: NYCT advertisements, ca. 2011
      Folder 23: NYCT video plan, 2011
      Folder 24: NYCT advertisements, 2012
      Folder 25: NYCT advertisements, 2014
      Folder 26: NYCT advertisements, 2015
      Folder 27: New York Community Trust: How Can This Equity Funder Rally Donors and Deepen Grassroots Engagement to Further Its Impact? (Philamplify Report by Lisa Ranghelli and Caitlin Duffy), April 2016
      Folder 28: NYCT advertisements, 2016
    - Advertisements and marketing, 2017-2024 (Offsite-box 5.5.2, Folder 1-10)
      Folder 1: NYCT advertisements, 2017
      Folder 2: Communications Strategy for the 100th Anniversary, June 11, 2018
      Folder 3: NYCT advertisements, 2019
      Folder 4: NYCT advertisements, 2022
      Folder 5: NYCT advertisements, 2023
      Folder 6: Market Research (Social Strategy Associates), October 2023
      Folder 7: Donor Engagement Research: Landscape Analysis (Social Strategy Associates), November 2023
      Folder 8: Donor Engagement Research: Key Insights and Recommendations (Social Strategy Associates), December 2023
      Folder 9: NYCT advertisements, December 2024
      Folder 10: NYCT advertisements, n.d.